gofreelance.com 2008-12-17

# Go Freelance: Privacy Statement

Go Freelance: Privacy Statement

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for:

We agree to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site  

  2. The organization collecting the information  

  3. How the information is used  

  4. With whom the information may be shared  

  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information  

  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the control of Go Freelance.  

  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information  

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact Rob Palmer by sending an email to [rob@gofreelance.com](mailto:rob@gofreelance.com). We will ensure that the issue is addressed promptly.

**Information Collection and Use**  
Go Freelance is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way. We collect names and email addresses only from visitors who ask to request our newsletter, free report and course of market tips. The information is used to send our newsletter, project updates, a free report and course of market tips.

**Registration**  
Visitors are not required to register to use the Go Freelance site, unless they wish to become members. Visitors can choose to become standard members (free) by providing an email address, which we use to mail newsletters and updates.

**Orders**  
Visitors can choose to upgrade to Professional Membership (paid subscription) by signing up through our order pages. We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer. We use third-party payment processors (iBill and Verotel) to handle payments. See the Sharing section for further information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use cookies to ensure that a popup newsletter subscription window is only seen once by each visitor, no matter how often the visitor returns. Visitors who refuse to accept cookies will see the popup window each time they visit. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze visitor trends and administer the site only. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing** We do not collect or share demographic or personal information with anyone.

We use CCBill, iBill and Verotel, established payment processing companies, to administer payments and control access to our password-protected members' area:

<http://www.ccbill.com/>

We also use Clickbank and Digibuy to administer other product and service purchases. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

Go Freelance may release personally identifiable information when required to by law.

**Links** This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Go Freelance is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Free Email Service**  
Visitors requesting a freelance-worker.com email address will be forwarded to Everyone.net, who manage this service. Everyone.net may request demographic information. We have no control over or access to this information

**Project Postings**  
Information collected from employers posting projects is used solely to create an appropriate job listing, and to facilitate communication with the employer. This information includes the employer's name and email address, plus details of the job requirement. 

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When a customer places an order, this will be handled on a secure server by our payment processors iBill, Verotel, Digibuy or Clickbank. All relevant precautions are taken by them to ensure a safe transaction. 

Go Freelance does not hold any information except for the name and email address details required for our mailing list. Only authorized personnel have access to the mailing list, and the database is backed up weekly to ensure data integrity.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to security@gofreelance.com. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:** Subscribers can update their personal information at any time by sending an email to [support@gofreelance.com](mailto:support@gofreelance.com)

**Communications**  
If visitors wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for their name and email address only as contact information. Subscribers will also receive Project Updates and Job of the Week information by email.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
We enforce a strict 'opt-in' only policy, where all our subscribers have specifically asked to be added to our mailing list. Visitors are not obliged to subscribe to our mailing list. Any subscriber can ask to be removed from the list at any time. Each mailing from Go Freelance includes a 'remove' link, which allows the subscriber to unsubscribe with a single click. Alternatively, subscribers can send an email to support@gofreelance.com and ask to be removed. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Inquiries**  
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact Rob Palmer using the contact information below. 

**Contact Information**  
Go Freelance can be contacted as follows:  
Email: [support@gofreelance.com](mailto:support@gofreelance.com)  
Tel: 718-249-4822 

Go Freelance  
45 Main Street  
Ste 309   
#178  
Brooklyn  
New York   
NY11201  
USA
